

## **David Griffin, Full Stack Web Developer**

I'm a hardworking, meticulous worker with an appetite to learn and work with various technologies. I have indispensable problem solving and critical thinking capabilities. Discovering and researching problems and delving into the unknown is my oxygen.

## **Employment History**

Customer Service Associate at Lowe's Home Improvement, Goodyear

January 2022 — Present

E-commerce Associate at Fry's Food Stores, Avondale

December 2019 — January 2022

Customer service regarding e-commerce orders. Gathering items for online customer orders and curbside pick-up. Using TIL to check out customers and solve coupon and order total problems. Customer service regarding refunds and exchanges. Informing customers on best products etc.

## Education

## Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, University of Arizona, Tucson

December 2021 — June 2022

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js. MySQL, MongoDB, Express.js, React.js and Object Oriented Programming

Diploma, Youngker High School, Buckeye

August 2015 — May 2019

Physics, Estrella Mountain Community College, Avondale

January 2020 — Present

LinkedIn

Links	<u>LinkedIn</u>	
Skills	<b>O</b> Git	jQuery
	React	O HTML & CSS
	O Node.js	O MySQL
	JavaScript	O css